{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570359629","data":{"timestamp":" 947570359629"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" b2a0405a-c656-4440-97e6-971442832f26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sauti_sauti-mwitu-arudi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sauti"," userResponse":" mwitu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570366777","data":{"timestamp":" 947570366777"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" b2a0405a-c656-4440-97e6-971442832f26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sauti_sauti-mwitu-arudi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sauti"," userResponse":" sauti"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570371866","data":{"timestamp":" 947570371866"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" b2a0405a-c656-4440-97e6-971442832f26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nyigu_nyigu-ukiwa-mjoma"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyigu"," userResponse":" nyigu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570379896","data":{"timestamp":" 947570379895"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" b2a0405a-c656-4440-97e6-971442832f26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbuni_mbuni-ndizi-ukiwa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbuni"," userResponse":" mbuni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570385922","data":{"timestamp":" 947570385921"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" b2a0405a-c656-4440-97e6-971442832f26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ofisi_vumbi-ofisi-mpaka"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ofisi"," userResponse":" ofisi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570390869","data":{"timestamp":" 947570390869"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" b2a0405a-c656-4440-97e6-971442832f26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mlima_mlima-mende-umati"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mlima"," userResponse":" mlima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570396663","data":{"timestamp":" 947570396663"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" b2a0405a-c656-4440-97e6-971442832f26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ambao_kindi-ambao-mzito"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ambao"," userResponse":" ambao"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570406322","data":{"timestamp":" 947570406322"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" b2a0405a-c656-4440-97e6-971442832f26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mpira_sivyo-swala-mpira"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mpira"," userResponse":" mpira"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570414848","data":{"timestamp":" 947570414848"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" b2a0405a-c656-4440-97e6-971442832f26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mende_treni-mende-mkoba"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mende"," userResponse":" treni"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570422067","data":{"timestamp":" 947570422067"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" b2a0405a-c656-4440-97e6-971442832f26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mende_treni-mende-mkoba"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mende"," userResponse":" mende"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570429502","data":{"timestamp":" 947570429502"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" b2a0405a-c656-4440-97e6-971442832f26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ndani_ndani-aliye-twiga"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ndani"," userResponse":" ndani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570436373","data":{"timestamp":" 947570436373"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" b2a0405a-c656-4440-97e6-971442832f26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_awali_mkuyu-awali-ndege"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" awali"," userResponse":" ndege"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570443395","data":{"timestamp":" 947570443395"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" b2a0405a-c656-4440-97e6-971442832f26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_awali_mkuyu-awali-ndege"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" awali"," userResponse":" ndege"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570456343","data":{"timestamp":" 947570456343"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" b2a0405a-c656-4440-97e6-971442832f26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_awali_mkuyu-awali-ndege"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" awali"," userResponse":" awali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570462133","data":{"timestamp":" 947570462132"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" b2a0405a-c656-4440-97e6-971442832f26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_awali_mkuyu-awali-ndege"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570483617","data":{"timestamp":" 947570483617"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 44bcbaa1-3f85-41d1-bae2-06778bd54d99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ndani_ndani-aliye-twiga"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ndani"," userResponse":" ndani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570492730","data":{"timestamp":" 947570492730"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 44bcbaa1-3f85-41d1-bae2-06778bd54d99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mlima_mlima-mende-umati"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mlima"," userResponse":" mlima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570500658","data":{"timestamp":" 947570500657"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 44bcbaa1-3f85-41d1-bae2-06778bd54d99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sauti_sauti-mwitu-arudi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sauti"," userResponse":" sauti"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570510632","data":{"timestamp":" 947570510632"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 44bcbaa1-3f85-41d1-bae2-06778bd54d99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ambao_kindi-ambao-mzito"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ambao"," userResponse":" ambao"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570520707","data":{"timestamp":" 947570520707"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 44bcbaa1-3f85-41d1-bae2-06778bd54d99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_awali_mkuyu-awali-ndege"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" awali"," userResponse":" ndege"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570527406","data":{"timestamp":" 947570527406"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 44bcbaa1-3f85-41d1-bae2-06778bd54d99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_awali_mkuyu-awali-ndege"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" awali"," userResponse":" mkuyu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570535544","data":{"timestamp":" 947570535544"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 44bcbaa1-3f85-41d1-bae2-06778bd54d99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_awali_mkuyu-awali-ndege"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" awali"," userResponse":" awali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570541299","data":{"timestamp":" 947570541299"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 44bcbaa1-3f85-41d1-bae2-06778bd54d99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nyigu_nyigu-ukiwa-mjoma"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyigu"," userResponse":" nyigu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570553037","data":{"timestamp":" 947570553036"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 44bcbaa1-3f85-41d1-bae2-06778bd54d99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbuni_mbuni-ndizi-ukiwa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbuni"," userResponse":" ndizi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570561440","data":{"timestamp":" 947570561440"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 44bcbaa1-3f85-41d1-bae2-06778bd54d99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbuni_mbuni-ndizi-ukiwa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbuni"," userResponse":" mbuni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570568030","data":{"timestamp":" 947570568030"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 44bcbaa1-3f85-41d1-bae2-06778bd54d99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mpira_sivyo-swala-mpira"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mpira"," userResponse":" swala"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570583476","data":{"timestamp":" 947570583476"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 44bcbaa1-3f85-41d1-bae2-06778bd54d99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mpira_sivyo-swala-mpira"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mpira"," userResponse":" mpira"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570590355","data":{"timestamp":" 947570590355"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 44bcbaa1-3f85-41d1-bae2-06778bd54d99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ofisi_vumbi-ofisi-mpaka"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ofisi"," userResponse":" ofisi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570596723","data":{"timestamp":" 947570596723"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 44bcbaa1-3f85-41d1-bae2-06778bd54d99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mende_treni-mende-mkoba"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mende"," userResponse":" mende"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570602496","data":{"timestamp":" 947570602494"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 44bcbaa1-3f85-41d1-bae2-06778bd54d99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_mende_treni-mende-mkoba"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570626995","data":{"timestamp":" 947570626995"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" fc6a121e-07f6-485e-ac07-bc58a67ad1c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbuni_mbuni-ndizi-ukiwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbuni"," userResponse":" mbuni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570635262","data":{"timestamp":" 947570635262"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" fc6a121e-07f6-485e-ac07-bc58a67ad1c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ambao_kindi-ambao-mzito"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ambao"," userResponse":" ambao"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570644628","data":{"timestamp":" 947570644628"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" fc6a121e-07f6-485e-ac07-bc58a67ad1c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mende_treni-mende-mkoba"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mende"," userResponse":" mende"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570657030","data":{"timestamp":" 947570657030"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" fc6a121e-07f6-485e-ac07-bc58a67ad1c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mlima_mlima-mende-umati"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mlima"," userResponse":" umati"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570664989","data":{"timestamp":" 947570664989"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" fc6a121e-07f6-485e-ac07-bc58a67ad1c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mlima_mlima-mende-umati"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mlima"," userResponse":" mlima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570678182","data":{"timestamp":" 947570678182"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" fc6a121e-07f6-485e-ac07-bc58a67ad1c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nyigu_nyigu-ukiwa-mjoma"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyigu"," userResponse":" nyigu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570695059","data":{"timestamp":" 947570695059"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" fc6a121e-07f6-485e-ac07-bc58a67ad1c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sauti_sauti-mwitu-arudi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sauti"," userResponse":" sauti"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570704981","data":{"timestamp":" 947570704981"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" fc6a121e-07f6-485e-ac07-bc58a67ad1c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mpira_sivyo-swala-mpira"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mpira"," userResponse":" mpira"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570714333","data":{"timestamp":" 947570714333"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" fc6a121e-07f6-485e-ac07-bc58a67ad1c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ofisi_vumbi-ofisi-mpaka"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ofisi"," userResponse":" ofisi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570723104","data":{"timestamp":" 947570723103"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" fc6a121e-07f6-485e-ac07-bc58a67ad1c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_awali_mkuyu-awali-ndege"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" awali"," userResponse":" awali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570735406","data":{"timestamp":" 947570735406"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" fc6a121e-07f6-485e-ac07-bc58a67ad1c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ndani_ndani-aliye-twiga"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ndani"," userResponse":" twiga"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570741565","data":{"timestamp":" 947570741564"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" fc6a121e-07f6-485e-ac07-bc58a67ad1c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ndani_ndani-aliye-twiga"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ndani"," userResponse":" ndani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570747308","data":{"timestamp":" 947570747306"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" fc6a121e-07f6-485e-ac07-bc58a67ad1c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_ndani_ndani-aliye-twiga"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570760899","data":{"timestamp":" 947570760898"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 7804ff9b-13da-4b56-a70a-4b05486c4035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kukaa_nyigu-kofia-kukaa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kukaa"," userResponse":" kukaa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570766019","data":{"timestamp":" 947570766019"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 7804ff9b-13da-4b56-a70a-4b05486c4035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_miguu_ofisi-mungu-miguu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" miguu"," userResponse":" miguu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570771839","data":{"timestamp":" 947570771839"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 7804ff9b-13da-4b56-a70a-4b05486c4035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alama_ikiwa-alama-tamaa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alama"," userResponse":" tamaa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570777709","data":{"timestamp":" 947570777709"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 7804ff9b-13da-4b56-a70a-4b05486c4035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alama_ikiwa-alama-tamaa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alama"," userResponse":" ikiwa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570783466","data":{"timestamp":" 947570783466"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 7804ff9b-13da-4b56-a70a-4b05486c4035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alama_ikiwa-alama-tamaa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alama"," userResponse":" alama"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570789331","data":{"timestamp":" 947570789330"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 7804ff9b-13da-4b56-a70a-4b05486c4035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kindi_kindi-pekee-hajui"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kindi"," userResponse":" hajui"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570796804","data":{"timestamp":" 947570796804"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 7804ff9b-13da-4b56-a70a-4b05486c4035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kindi_kindi-pekee-hajui"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kindi"," userResponse":" pekee"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570803059","data":{"timestamp":" 947570803058"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 7804ff9b-13da-4b56-a70a-4b05486c4035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kindi_kindi-pekee-hajui"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kindi"," userResponse":" kindi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570808921","data":{"timestamp":" 947570808921"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 7804ff9b-13da-4b56-a70a-4b05486c4035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tamaa_kizee-tamaa-vipya"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tamaa"," userResponse":" kizee"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570814800","data":{"timestamp":" 947570814800"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 7804ff9b-13da-4b56-a70a-4b05486c4035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tamaa_kizee-tamaa-vipya"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tamaa"," userResponse":" vipya"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570821676","data":{"timestamp":" 947570821676"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 7804ff9b-13da-4b56-a70a-4b05486c4035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tamaa_kizee-tamaa-vipya"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tamaa"," userResponse":" tamaa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570829671","data":{"timestamp":" 947570829671"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 7804ff9b-13da-4b56-a70a-4b05486c4035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_asije_asije-mengi-wingi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" asije"," userResponse":" asije"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570831213","data":{"timestamp":" 947570831213"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 7804ff9b-13da-4b56-a70a-4b05486c4035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_asije_asije-mengi-wingi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570855899","data":{"timestamp":" 947570855899"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" cae4fd6d-f84f-4693-92a1-354e2659b470"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alama_ikiwa-alama-tamaa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alama"," userResponse":" alama"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570864277","data":{"timestamp":" 947570864277"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" cae4fd6d-f84f-4693-92a1-354e2659b470"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kindi_kindi-pekee-hajui"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kindi"," userResponse":" hajui"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570868579","data":{"timestamp":" 947570868579"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" cae4fd6d-f84f-4693-92a1-354e2659b470"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kindi_kindi-pekee-hajui"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570900919","data":{"timestamp":" 947570900918"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570901549","data":{"timestamp":" 947570901549"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570902343","data":{"timestamp":" 947570902343"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHETU"," userResponse":" CHETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570903510","data":{"timestamp":" 947570903509"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANAISHI"," userResponse":" PANAISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570903966","data":{"timestamp":" 947570903965"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570904758","data":{"timestamp":" 947570904757"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIIO"," userResponse":" KIIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570907860","data":{"timestamp":" 947570907859"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" START_KATIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570909025","data":{"timestamp":" 947570909025"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570916099","data":{"timestamp":" 947570916099"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570920873","data":{"timestamp":" 947570920872"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIIO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570922503","data":{"timestamp":" 947570922502"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570924878","data":{"timestamp":" 947570924878"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHETU"," userResponse":" CHETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570926662","data":{"timestamp":" 947570926662"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANAISHI"," userResponse":" PANAISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570927963","data":{"timestamp":" 947570927963"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570929096","data":{"timestamp":" 947570929095"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIIO"," userResponse":" KIIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570930715","data":{"timestamp":" 947570930714"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570931551","data":{"timestamp":" 947570931550"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIIO"," userResponse":" KIIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570932397","data":{"timestamp":" 947570932397"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570933045","data":{"timestamp":" 947570933045"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKA"," userResponse":" PAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570933281","data":{"timestamp":" 947570933281"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570934020","data":{"timestamp":" 947570934019"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MADOA"," userResponse":" MADOA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570934880","data":{"timestamp":" 947570934880"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEUSI"," userResponse":" MEUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570935089","data":{"timestamp":" 947570935088"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570935930","data":{"timestamp":" 947570935930"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEUPE"," userResponse":" MEUPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570936540","data":{"timestamp":" 947570936539"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570937078","data":{"timestamp":" 947570937078"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570937921","data":{"timestamp":" 947570937920"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570939963","data":{"timestamp":" 947570939963"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570940481","data":{"timestamp":" 947570940480"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIIO"," userResponse":" KIIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570941378","data":{"timestamp":" 947570941378"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570941955","data":{"timestamp":" 947570941955"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKA"," userResponse":" PAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570942924","data":{"timestamp":" 947570942923"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570944227","data":{"timestamp":" 947570944227"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MADOA"," userResponse":" MADOA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570945055","data":{"timestamp":" 947570945055"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEUSI"," userResponse":" MEUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570947799","data":{"timestamp":" 947570947798"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570948867","data":{"timestamp":" 947570948867"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" PAKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570950306","data":{"timestamp":" 947570950306"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570952292","data":{"timestamp":" 947570952291"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MEUPE"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570954312","data":{"timestamp":" 947570954312"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MEUPE"," userResponse":" PAKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570955896","data":{"timestamp":" 947570955895"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEUPE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570957565","data":{"timestamp":" 947570957565"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570961244","data":{"timestamp":" 947570961243"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570963392","data":{"timestamp":" 947570963391"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570970346","data":{"timestamp":" 947570970345"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570972484","data":{"timestamp":" 947570972484"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio anapoenda kazini anaacha mlango wazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570973231","data":{"timestamp":" 947570973231"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio anapoenda kazini anaacha mlango wazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIIO"," userResponse":" KIIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570974290","data":{"timestamp":" 947570974289"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio anapoenda kazini anaacha mlango wazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPOENDA"," userResponse":" ANAPOENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570975249","data":{"timestamp":" 947570975248"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio anapoenda kazini anaacha mlango wazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZINI"," userResponse":" KAZINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570976459","data":{"timestamp":" 947570976458"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio anapoenda kazini anaacha mlango wazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAACHA"," userResponse":" ANAACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570977082","data":{"timestamp":" 947570977081"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio anapoenda kazini anaacha mlango wazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" MLANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570977849","data":{"timestamp":" 947570977848"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio anapoenda kazini anaacha mlango wazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZI"," userResponse":" WAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570981907","data":{"timestamp":" 947570981907"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio anapoenda kazini anaacha mlango wazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570984746","data":{"timestamp":" 947570984746"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio anapoenda kazini anaacha mlango wazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIIO"," userResponse":" ANAACHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570991553","data":{"timestamp":" 947570991552"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio anapoenda kazini anaacha mlango wazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIIO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570997013","data":{"timestamp":" 947570997012"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio anapoenda kazini anaacha mlango wazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPOENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571000475","data":{"timestamp":" 947571000475"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio anapoenda kazini anaacha mlango wazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KAZINI"," userResponse":" START_KAZINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571005500","data":{"timestamp":" 947571005500"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio anapoenda kazini anaacha mlango wazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571010936","data":{"timestamp":" 947571010936"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio anapoenda kazini anaacha mlango wazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAACHA"," userResponse":" ANAACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571020339","data":{"timestamp":" 947571020338"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio anapoenda kazini anaacha mlango wazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571025416","data":{"timestamp":" 947571025415"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio anapoenda kazini anaacha mlango wazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571027910","data":{"timestamp":" 947571027909"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571028860","data":{"timestamp":" 947571028860"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKAA"," userResponse":" ANAKAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571029968","data":{"timestamp":" 947571029967"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571030057","data":{"timestamp":" 947571030057"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571030937","data":{"timestamp":" 947571030937"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" MLANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571031545","data":{"timestamp":" 947571031545"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571032425","data":{"timestamp":" 947571032425"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUILINDA"," userResponse":" KUILINDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571032983","data":{"timestamp":" 947571032982"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571033201","data":{"timestamp":" 947571033200"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571033680","data":{"timestamp":" 947571033680"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571034471","data":{"timestamp":" 947571034470"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIIO"," userResponse":" KIIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571037346","data":{"timestamp":" 947571037345"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571037359","data":{"timestamp":" 947571037359"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKAA"," userResponse":" ANAKAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571039842","data":{"timestamp":" 947571039842"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" ANAKAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571043385","data":{"timestamp":" 947571043385"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571044536","data":{"timestamp":" 947571044536"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571046017","data":{"timestamp":" 947571046016"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571050234","data":{"timestamp":" 947571050234"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571057202","data":{"timestamp":" 947571057201"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571063610","data":{"timestamp":" 947571063610"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUILINDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571071149","data":{"timestamp":" 947571071148"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571071517","data":{"timestamp":" 947571071516"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571072026","data":{"timestamp":" 947571072026"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571072943","data":{"timestamp":" 947571072943"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIIO"," userResponse":" KIIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571075230","data":{"timestamp":" 947571075229"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBWA"," userResponse":" MBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571075425","data":{"timestamp":" 947571075424"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571076229","data":{"timestamp":" 947571076228"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIRANI"," userResponse":" JIRANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571077668","data":{"timestamp":" 947571077668"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIKARIBIA"," userResponse":" AKIKARIBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571078655","data":{"timestamp":" 947571078655"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571080511","data":{"timestamp":" 947571080511"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMKODOLEA"," userResponse":" ANAMKODOLEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571081222","data":{"timestamp":" 947571081221"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571081769","data":{"timestamp":" 947571081768"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571083188","data":{"timestamp":" 947571083187"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMUNYOOSHEA"," userResponse":" KUMUNYOOSHEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571083927","data":{"timestamp":" 947571083926"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHA"," userResponse":" KUCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571084728","data":{"timestamp":" 947571084727"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571091754","data":{"timestamp":" 947571091753"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MBWA"," userResponse":" START_MBWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571095844","data":{"timestamp":" 947571095843"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571098593","data":{"timestamp":" 947571098593"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571100824","data":{"timestamp":" 947571100824"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIRANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571102824","data":{"timestamp":" 947571102824"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKIKARIBIA"," userResponse":" START_AKIKARIBIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571108279","data":{"timestamp":" 947571108278"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIKARIBIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571112330","data":{"timestamp":" 947571112330"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571115942","data":{"timestamp":" 947571115942"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571119408","data":{"timestamp":" 947571119408"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMKODOLEA"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571121181","data":{"timestamp":" 947571121180"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMKODOLEA"," userResponse":" START_ANAMKODOLEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571123102","data":{"timestamp":" 947571123101"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMKODOLEA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571129443","data":{"timestamp":" 947571129443"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571131945","data":{"timestamp":" 947571131944"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" MBWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571134997","data":{"timestamp":" 947571134997"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571138819","data":{"timestamp":" 947571138819"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUMUNYOOSHEA"," userResponse":" JIRANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571142214","data":{"timestamp":" 947571142213"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMUNYOOSHEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571147717","data":{"timestamp":" 947571147717"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571149503","data":{"timestamp":" 947571149503"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571151871","data":{"timestamp":" 947571151870"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa anatoroka na kurudi kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBWA"," userResponse":" MBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571153403","data":{"timestamp":" 947571153403"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa anatoroka na kurudi kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANATOROKA"," userResponse":" ANATOROKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571153698","data":{"timestamp":" 947571153697"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa anatoroka na kurudi kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571154366","data":{"timestamp":" 947571154365"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa anatoroka na kurudi kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUDI"," userResponse":" KURUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571154822","data":{"timestamp":" 947571154821"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa anatoroka na kurudi kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAO"," userResponse":" KWAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571157280","data":{"timestamp":" 947571157280"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa anatoroka na kurudi kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBWA"," userResponse":" MBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571158669","data":{"timestamp":" 947571158669"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa anatoroka na kurudi kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANATOROKA"," userResponse":" ANATOROKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571159667","data":{"timestamp":" 947571159667"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa anatoroka na kurudi kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571159679","data":{"timestamp":" 947571159678"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa anatoroka na kurudi kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUDI"," userResponse":" KURUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571160086","data":{"timestamp":" 947571160085"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa anatoroka na kurudi kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAO"," userResponse":" KWAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571162714","data":{"timestamp":" 947571162713"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani akitokezea Safi yu tayari kumkwaruza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIRANI"," userResponse":" JIRANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571164333","data":{"timestamp":" 947571164332"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani akitokezea Safi yu tayari kumkwaruza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKITOKEZEA"," userResponse":" AKITOKEZEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571165694","data":{"timestamp":" 947571165694"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani akitokezea Safi yu tayari kumkwaruza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571165961","data":{"timestamp":" 947571165960"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani akitokezea Safi yu tayari kumkwaruza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YU"," userResponse":" YU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571166962","data":{"timestamp":" 947571166962"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani akitokezea Safi yu tayari kumkwaruza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TAYARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571168438","data":{"timestamp":" 947571168437"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani akitokezea Safi yu tayari kumkwaruza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMKWARUZA"," userResponse":" KUMKWARUZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571170871","data":{"timestamp":" 947571170871"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani akitokezea Safi yu tayari kumkwaruza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIRANI"," userResponse":" JIRANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571171361","data":{"timestamp":" 947571171360"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani akitokezea Safi yu tayari kumkwaruza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKITOKEZEA"," userResponse":" START_AKITOKEZEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571173774","data":{"timestamp":" 947571173773"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani akitokezea Safi yu tayari kumkwaruza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKITOKEZEA"," userResponse":" AKITOKEZEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571180223","data":{"timestamp":" 947571180223"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani akitokezea Safi yu tayari kumkwaruza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571182270","data":{"timestamp":" 947571182269"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani akitokezea Safi yu tayari kumkwaruza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YU"," userResponse":" YU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571182605","data":{"timestamp":" 947571182605"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani akitokezea Safi yu tayari kumkwaruza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" START_TAYARI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571184119","data":{"timestamp":" 947571184119"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani akitokezea Safi yu tayari kumkwaruza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" KUMKWARUZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571185900","data":{"timestamp":" 947571185900"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani akitokezea Safi yu tayari kumkwaruza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571194508","data":{"timestamp":" 947571194508"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani akitokezea Safi yu tayari kumkwaruza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMKWARUZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571197126","data":{"timestamp":" 947571197125"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani anageuka mbio na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIRANI"," userResponse":" JIRANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571198293","data":{"timestamp":" 947571198292"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani anageuka mbio na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAGEUKA"," userResponse":" ANAGEUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571199043","data":{"timestamp":" 947571199042"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani anageuka mbio na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBIO"," userResponse":" MBIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571199647","data":{"timestamp":" 947571199647"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani anageuka mbio na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571200217","data":{"timestamp":" 947571200216"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani anageuka mbio na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571200762","data":{"timestamp":" 947571200762"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani anageuka mbio na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571203031","data":{"timestamp":" 947571203031"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani anageuka mbio na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIRANI"," userResponse":" JIRANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571203660","data":{"timestamp":" 947571203659"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani anageuka mbio na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANAGEUKA"," userResponse":" START_ANAGEUKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571204674","data":{"timestamp":" 947571204673"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani anageuka mbio na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANAGEUKA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571206471","data":{"timestamp":" 947571206470"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani anageuka mbio na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAGEUKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571208743","data":{"timestamp":" 947571208742"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani anageuka mbio na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBIO"," userResponse":" MBIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571208761","data":{"timestamp":" 947571208760"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani anageuka mbio na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571208777","data":{"timestamp":" 947571208776"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani anageuka mbio na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571209171","data":{"timestamp":" 947571209171"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani anageuka mbio na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571211744","data":{"timestamp":" 947571211743"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akihisi njaa anafunga mlango kwa kuusukuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571212670","data":{"timestamp":" 947571212669"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akihisi njaa anafunga mlango kwa kuusukuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIHISI"," userResponse":" AKIHISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571213417","data":{"timestamp":" 947571213416"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akihisi njaa anafunga mlango kwa kuusukuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571214727","data":{"timestamp":" 947571214726"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akihisi njaa anafunga mlango kwa kuusukuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFUNGA"," userResponse":" ANAFUNGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571215493","data":{"timestamp":" 947571215492"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akihisi njaa anafunga mlango kwa kuusukuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" MLANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571215751","data":{"timestamp":" 947571215750"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akihisi njaa anafunga mlango kwa kuusukuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571217239","data":{"timestamp":" 947571217239"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akihisi njaa anafunga mlango kwa kuusukuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUSUKUMA"," userResponse":" KUUSUKUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571219455","data":{"timestamp":" 947571219454"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akihisi njaa anafunga mlango kwa kuusukuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571220052","data":{"timestamp":" 947571220052"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akihisi njaa anafunga mlango kwa kuusukuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKIHISI"," userResponse":" START_AKIHISI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571220995","data":{"timestamp":" 947571220995"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akihisi njaa anafunga mlango kwa kuusukuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKIHISI"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571222880","data":{"timestamp":" 947571222879"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akihisi njaa anafunga mlango kwa kuusukuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIHISI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571224479","data":{"timestamp":" 947571224479"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akihisi njaa anafunga mlango kwa kuusukuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" AKIHISI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571225769","data":{"timestamp":" 947571225769"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akihisi njaa anafunga mlango kwa kuusukuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571226273","data":{"timestamp":" 947571226272"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akihisi njaa anafunga mlango kwa kuusukuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFUNGA"," userResponse":" ANAFUNGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571228094","data":{"timestamp":" 947571228093"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akihisi njaa anafunga mlango kwa kuusukuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571232430","data":{"timestamp":" 947571232429"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akihisi njaa anafunga mlango kwa kuusukuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571238397","data":{"timestamp":" 947571238397"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akihisi njaa anafunga mlango kwa kuusukuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571241809","data":{"timestamp":" 947571241809"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akihisi njaa anafunga mlango kwa kuusukuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUSUKUMA"," userResponse":" KUUSUKUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571244779","data":{"timestamp":" 947571244778"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaingia ndani na kula chakula chake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAINGIA"," userResponse":" ANAINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571245412","data":{"timestamp":" 947571245412"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaingia ndani na kula chakula chake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571245647","data":{"timestamp":" 947571245646"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaingia ndani na kula chakula chake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571246242","data":{"timestamp":" 947571246241"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaingia ndani na kula chakula chake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571247029","data":{"timestamp":" 947571247029"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaingia ndani na kula chakula chake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571247786","data":{"timestamp":" 947571247785"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaingia ndani na kula chakula chake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKE"," userResponse":" CHAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571253680","data":{"timestamp":" 947571253680"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaingia ndani na kula chakula chake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAINGIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571255527","data":{"timestamp":" 947571255527"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaingia ndani na kula chakula chake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571257764","data":{"timestamp":" 947571257764"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaingia ndani na kula chakula chake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571259486","data":{"timestamp":" 947571259486"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaingia ndani na kula chakula chake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571261492","data":{"timestamp":" 947571261492"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaingia ndani na kula chakula chake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571264370","data":{"timestamp":" 947571264370"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaingia ndani na kula chakula chake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571266208","data":{"timestamp":" 947571266208"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaingia ndani na kula chakula chake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571268756","data":{"timestamp":" 947571268755"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571270346","data":{"timestamp":" 947571270345"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIMALIZA"," userResponse":" AKIMALIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571271738","data":{"timestamp":" 947571271738"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANARUKA"," userResponse":" ANARUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571272455","data":{"timestamp":" 947571272454"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571272702","data":{"timestamp":" 947571272701"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571273309","data":{"timestamp":" 947571273309"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOFA"," userResponse":" SOFA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571273536","data":{"timestamp":" 947571273535"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571274384","data":{"timestamp":" 947571274384"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" KULALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571276685","data":{"timestamp":" 947571276684"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571277530","data":{"timestamp":" 947571277530"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKIMALIZA"," userResponse":" START_AKIMALIZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571278561","data":{"timestamp":" 947571278560"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKIMALIZA"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571280477","data":{"timestamp":" 947571280476"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIMALIZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571283454","data":{"timestamp":" 947571283454"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANARUKA"," userResponse":" ANARUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571283457","data":{"timestamp":" 947571283457"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571284520","data":{"timestamp":" 947571284520"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571288075","data":{"timestamp":" 947571288075"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOFA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571290102","data":{"timestamp":" 947571290102"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571294685","data":{"timestamp":" 947571294684"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571297772","data":{"timestamp":" 947571297771"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571300527","data":{"timestamp":" 947571300526"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unachosikia ni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNACHOSIKIA"," userResponse":" UNACHOSIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571300914","data":{"timestamp":" 947571300913"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unachosikia ni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571301860","data":{"timestamp":" 947571301859"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unachosikia ni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PURR"," userResponse":" PURR"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571304889","data":{"timestamp":" 947571304889"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unachosikia ni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNACHOSIKIA"," userResponse":" UNACHOSIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571304899","data":{"timestamp":" 947571304899"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unachosikia ni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571305430","data":{"timestamp":" 947571305429"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unachosikia ni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PURR"," userResponse":" PURR"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571307728","data":{"timestamp":" 947571307727"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571308700","data":{"timestamp":" 947571308698"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIIO"," userResponse":" KIIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571310217","data":{"timestamp":" 947571310216"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWASILI"," userResponse":" AKIWASILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571311234","data":{"timestamp":" 947571311233"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571312672","data":{"timestamp":" 947571312671"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUJINYOOSHA"," userResponse":" HUJINYOOSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571314500","data":{"timestamp":" 947571314499"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571315671","data":{"timestamp":" 947571315670"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571315958","data":{"timestamp":" 947571315958"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571317273","data":{"timestamp":" 947571317272"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMKARIBISHA"," userResponse":" KUMKARIBISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571318337","data":{"timestamp":" 947571318336"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571321483","data":{"timestamp":" 947571321482"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571322448","data":{"timestamp":" 947571322447"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" KIIO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571323902","data":{"timestamp":" 947571323902"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571325051","data":{"timestamp":" 947571325050"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIIO"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571326666","data":{"timestamp":" 947571326666"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIIO"," userResponse":" KIIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571329134","data":{"timestamp":" 947571329133"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWASILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571330797","data":{"timestamp":" 947571330797"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571331620","data":{"timestamp":" 947571331620"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" KIIO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571333257","data":{"timestamp":" 947571333257"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571334217","data":{"timestamp":" 947571334217"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HUJINYOOSHA"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571335333","data":{"timestamp":" 947571335333"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUJINYOOSHA"," userResponse":" HUJINYOOSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571337405","data":{"timestamp":" 947571337404"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571340705","data":{"timestamp":" 947571340705"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571341259","data":{"timestamp":" 947571341258"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571345920","data":{"timestamp":" 947571345920"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMKARIBISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571348177","data":{"timestamp":" 947571348177"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571351416","data":{"timestamp":" 947571351416"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571351950","data":{"timestamp":" 947571351950"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571353580","data":{"timestamp":" 947571353579"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIIO"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571354257","data":{"timestamp":" 947571354256"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" KIIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571354472","data":{"timestamp":" 947571354472"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571355080","data":{"timestamp":" 947571355080"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAKETI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571356263","data":{"timestamp":" 947571356262"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" WANAKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571356962","data":{"timestamp":" 947571356961"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571357251","data":{"timestamp":" 947571357250"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571358186","data":{"timestamp":" 947571358185"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571359301","data":{"timestamp":" 947571359300"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571360185","data":{"timestamp":" 947571360185"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKISOMA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571361408","data":{"timestamp":" 947571361408"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GAZETI"," userResponse":" AKISOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571374051","data":{"timestamp":" 947571374050"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947571374150","data":{"timestamp":" 947571374150"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_085904"," gameId":" 1674aec8-e617-4142-ba0c-85b93c9331fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GAZETI"," userResponse":" AKISOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}